//creating an array and passing the number, question, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question:"Which two nations won the Copa America most times?",
        answer: "Argentina and Uruguay",
        options:[
            "Chile and Brazil",
            "Brazil and Argentina",
            "Uruguay and Mexico",
            "Argentina and Uruguay"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question:"Which was the first non south American nation to reach the final in 1993?",
        answer: "Mexico",
        options:[
            "Japan",
            "Canada",
            "Mexico",
            "USA"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question:"When did Colombia won their first Euro?",
        answer: "2001",
        options:[
            "2001",
            "1995",
            "1990",
            "1986"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question:"When was the Copa America centenario played of completing their 100 years?",
        answer: "2016",
        options:[
            "2008",
            "2021",
            "2016",
            "1995"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question:"Which country is the first non-south American team to host the Tournament?",
        answer: "USA",
        options:[
            "Canada",
            "USA",
            "Cuba",
            "Mexico"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question:"What is the highest goal scoring match in the history of Copa America?",
        answer: "Argentina 12-0 Ecuador",
        options:[
            "Brazil 14-4 Boilvia",
            "Chile 10-2 USA",
            "Argentina 12-0 Ecuador",
            "Argentina 14-0 Paraguay"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question:"Who is the highest goal scorer of the Copa America?",
        answer: "Norberto Mendez",
        options:[
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Norberto Mendez",
            "Severino Varela",
            "Zizinho"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question:"Copa America previously know as the South Football Championship when did the compition changed its name ?",
        answer: "1975",
        options:[
            "1960",
            "1978",
            "1974",
            "1975"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question:"Which country has made the most appearances in the Copa America finals?(28)",
        answer: "Argentina",
        options:[
            "Argentina",
            "Mexico",
            "Uruguay",
            "Chile"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question:"Who scored the fastest Hat-trick completed as substitute in tournament History?",
        answer: "Lionel Messi",
        options:[
            "Kily Gonzalez",
            "Sergio Livingstone",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Jose Manuel Moreno"
        ]
    },
];